[{"question":"# Q1. Scala bytecode can run on top of Java VM. What is the fundamental difference between Java object.clone() and Scala object.copy()?","options":["One is a Java object, the other is a Scala object.","clone() will copy class structures but not the data, while copy() will also copy data into new objects.","There is no difference.","copy() allows you to change values during the copying process; clone() does not."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"copy() allows you to change values during the copying process; clone() does not."},{"question":"# Q2. What value does this code return?\n```\nval m1 = Map(\"a\"->1,\"b\"->2,\"c\"->3)\nm1(\"a\")\n\n```","options":["a","2","b","1"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"1"},{"question":"# Q3. What is one way to avoid low-level parallelization details?","options":["monads","literal functions","partially applied functions","parallel collections"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"parallel collections"},{"question":"# Q4. What do you use in ScalaTest to see a detailed diagram of error messages when a test fails?","options":["ArgumentExceptions","AssertionException","DiagrammedAssertions","JUnit"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"DiagrammedAssertions"},{"question":"# Q5. What data type would you use to store an immutable collection of objects that contain a fixed number of varying types?","options":["Array","ImmutableCollection","List","Tuple"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Tuple"},{"question":"# Q6. After defining a function in the interpreter, Scala returns the following. What does the\n```\nmyfnc: ()Unit\n\n```","options":["The function has no side effects.","The function takes no parameters.","The function returns no value.","Returning unit types to the function is a closures."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"The function returns no value."},{"question":"# Q7. What type of number is 1234.e5?","options":["hexadecimal","short","floating point","long"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"floating point"},{"question":"# Q8. When you convert a map to a list using the toList method of the map, the result will be of which type?","options":["List[(String, String)]","List[(Array, Array)]","List[(Array, Array)]","List"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"List"},{"question":"# Q9. What type of object does this code create?\n```\nval x = (1234, \"Active\")\n\n```","options":["List","Map","Tuple","Array"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Tuple"},{"question":"# Q10. Which is a subclass of all classes?","options":["AnyVal","AnyRef","Method","Null NOT SURE"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Null NOT SURE"},{"question":"# Q11. For the for-yield construct, is the scope separate between for-body and yield-body?","options":["Yes and no. It is different depending on the for construct and what it does. NOT SURE","Yes, because the for section does not expose its scope.","No, because for-yield shares the same scope, even though they are within separate curly braces.","Yes, because they are within different curly braces."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Yes and no. It is different depending on the for construct and what it does. NOT SURE"},{"question":"# Q12. What is one way to implement pattern matching on methods?","options":["using regex","using monads","using string matching","using case classes"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"using string matching"},{"question":"# Q13. What is the value of z after executing this code?\n```\nval y = List('a','b')\nval z = y::List('c')\n\n```","options":["List(a,b,c)","List(List(a, b), c)","List(c,a,b)","List(c,List(a,b))"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"List(List(a, b), c)"},{"question":"# Q14. What term is used to specify a precondition?","options":["assert","require","precondition","mustHave"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"assert"},{"question":"# Q15. Which Scala type may throw an exception or a successfully computed value, and is commonly used to trap and propagate errors?","options":[]},{"question":"## answers missing","options":["Answer should be Option: Some or None"]},{"question":"# Q16. What is the data type of y after this code is executed?\n```\nval y = (math floor 3.1415 * 2)\n\n```","options":["short","double","int","bigInt"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"double"},{"question":"# Q17. When using pattern matching, which character matches on any object?","options":["%","\\_","^","-"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"-"},{"question":"# Q18. You have created an array using val. Can you change the value of any element of the arrayâ€”and why or why not?","options":["Yes, the reference to the array is immutable, so the location that the array points to is immutable. The values in the array are mutable.","The 0th element is immutable and cannot be modified. All other elements can be modified.","Yes, val does not make arrays immutable.","No, val makes the array and values of the array immutable."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Yes, val does not make arrays immutable."},{"question":"# Q19. What is the output of this function?\n```\ndef main () {\n     var a = 0\n     for (a<-1 until 5){println(a)}\n\n```","options":["1,2,3,4,5","0,1,2,3,4","1,2,3,4","2,3,4,5"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"1,2,3,4"},{"question":"# Q20. What do you call objects with immutable state?","options":["singletons","stationary objects","functional objects","fixed objects"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"singletons"},{"question":"# Q21. You have written a Scala script. How would you access command-line arguments in the script?","options":["use array named args","use tuple named args","use numbered variables with a _ prefix for example _ 1, _ 2, _ 3","use numbered variables with a $ prefix - for example $1, $2, $3"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"use array named args"},{"question":"# Q22. What does this code return? val x = 3; if (x >2) x = 4 else x = x\\*2","options":["4","an error","6","3"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"an error"},{"question":"# Q23. Which statement returns a success or a failure indicator when you execute this code?","options":["val MyFuture = Future {runBackgroundFunction() }","myFuture.onComplete","myFuture(status)","myFuture.Finished","complete(myFuture)"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"myFuture.onComplete"},{"question":"# Q24. To denote a parameter that may be repeated, what should you place after type?","options":["%","&","\\_","-"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"-"},{"question":"# Q25. What is called when a superclass has more than one subclass in Scala?","options":["polyinheritance","multilevel inheritance","multimode inheritance","hierarchical inheritance"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"hierarchical inheritance"}]